Guide to the Student Association records, 1935-2005 RG0023
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Student government records, 1935-2005; RG0023 Series 8; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains invitations, guides, a bookmark, brochures, correspondence, programs, memorandums, newsletters, stickers, reports, telegram, press releases, and posters. They range in date from 1935 to 2005. They materials concern the student government, the Student Association (SA), Student Council, the Student Council's Planning Commission, the Student Union, the history of the student government, elections, abolishment of the student government, student government officers, student political parties (left, center, right, service), communism, fascism, "The Left Party Speaks", "The Frontier: an independent journal of student opinion", the student government's constitution, the All-University Assembly, the Governing Board, the Operations Board of the University Center, an All University Government, organizational chart, priorities, services, charters, "GW Updates", "SA Update", SA Presidents, the Center for Academic Evaluation, and other activities.
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--GW Student Association (GWUSA), 1978-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--GW Student Association (GWUSA) - Charter, 05/20/1976 -1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clubs, Societies, Organizations--GW Student Association (GWUSA)--Publications, 1980 -05/20/2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Student government, 1936-2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student government - student council, 1937 ca. -10/31/1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student government - student council - Planning Commission annual report, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Student government - student union, 1935-1936, 11/18/1935 -12/01/1937 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Student government - university governance, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Barry Epstein Constitutional Convention and Student Association papers, 1971-1977; 1975-1977; RG0023 Series 9; 0.5 Linear Feet 1 document box
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, reports, memos, notes, agendas, publicity, and other documents created and collected by George Washington University alumnus Barry Epstein as a member of the George Washington University Constitutional Convention in 1975 and 1976. The materials document the efforts of students to reestablish student governance at the University, and the founding of the Student Association. Records date between 1971 and 1977.
  - Constitutional Convention Binder [1/3], circa 1975-1977; RG0023 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitutional Convention Binder [2/3], circa 1975-1977; RG0023 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constitutional Convention Binder [3/3], circa 1975-1977; RG0023 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constitutional Convention Committee Agendas, Minutes, and Reports, February 1975-January 1976; RG0023 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constitutional Convention Committee Notes, Agendas, Correspondence, Reports, Publicity, and Charter, 1971-1977; RG0023 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constitutional Convention Preliminary Committee Reports in Article Form, circa 1975-1976; RG0023 Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Joint Elections Committee records, 2010-2011; RG0023 Series 10; 1.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains records from the Joint Elections Committee, including candidacy statements, petitions, complaints and financial expense reports dating from 2010-2011.
  - Reports, 2010-2011 (Box 1)
  - Reports, 2010-2011 (Box 2)
- Kuyomars "Q" Golparvar collection of GW student association records, 1975-1998; Series 11; 4.5 Linear Feet 3 record center boxes (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series contains of records generated and collected by former President of the Student Body (1997-1998) Kuyomars "Q" Golparvar. Materials include GW student association records, Constitutional Convention records, Budget Advisory Team records and other materials amassed by Golparvar. Many of the records predate his actual involvement with the GW student association; he collected and preserved them during his tenure.
  - Budget Advisory Team materials, 1990-1992; 6 folder(s) (Box 1)
  - Constitution Convention Agendas and Minutes, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Constitution Convention Budgets and Reports, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Constitution Convention Reports, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Constitution Convention Reports and Appendix, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sterling Committee and Standing Committee materials, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Joint Committee of Faculty and Students, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Student Association manual (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Student Association Finance Committee guidebook (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Program Board manual, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Commencement town hall address, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs Committee Board of Trustees report, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Thurston Hal council, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Ambassadors lecture series, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)